prague.tv 2018-06-29

# Privacy | About

**We have updated our Privacy Policy. The updated Privacy Policy (which we encourage you to read) will go into effect on May 25, 2018 as part of compliance to the standards defined for data protection in the European Union (EU) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).**

The following policy is intended to explain how your personal information will be treated as you make use of our site and its features. 

## USER ACCOUNTS

All previous user accounts have been deactivated and user information was deleted. From now on all advertising and postings will be managed by our admin team. With this also our weekly Prague.TV newsletter service has stopped. 

## INSTANT EMAIL RESPONSE FEATURES 

Prague TV offers an " **APPLY** " feature, allowing site visitors to send an e-mail to the address provided by the bulletin board post submitter. In order for this feature to function, we ask for e-mail addresses for the recipient (so we know who to mail the message to) and from the sender (so we can tell the recipient who sent the e-mail). **We do not store or save these addresses and you will not receive e-mail or other communications from Prague TV or any of our partners as a result of having used this feature**. 

" **APPLY**   **by email** " is a mail service that individual visitors to Prague TV make use of to send individual e-mails. While this tool cannot be used to send mass "spam" mailings, Prague TV has no control over how our visitors use it, and any e-mail sent through it originates with and is the responsibility of, the sender, not Prague TV.

## OTHER DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION 

Prague TV will not otherwise use or disclose your personal information without your consent except (i) as described in this privacy policy, or (ii) as required by law, court order or as requested by other government or law enforcement authority. This policy does not protect the information you post to the Classified board on our website. 

## OTHER SITES 

Prague TV contains many links to other sites on the Web. We cannot control and are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of such other Web sites. 

## COOKIE POLICY

This website uses cookies to improve the user experience and ensure that it is functioning effectively, and on occasion also to provide marketing information or advertise online, either directly or through third-party vendors.

The website contains ‘social buttons’ that enable users to share or bookmark web pages. These are buttons for third party social media sites and these sites may log information about your activities on the Internet including on this website. Zomato sometimes also uses external web services on this website to display content within the web pages of this website, for example, to display images, show videos or run polls. As with the social buttons, Prague.TV cannot prevent these sites, or external domains, from collecting information on your use of this embedded content. Please review the respective terms of use and privacy policies/statements/notices of these sites, or external domains to understand exactly how they use your information and to find out how to opt-out, or delete such information.

## WHO CAN I ASK IF I HAVE ADDITIONAL QUESTIONS 

If you have any further questions or concerns about our privacy policy and use of personal information, please send them to [info@prague.tv](mailto:info@prague.tv) or use our contact form.
